There are so many of them!
I can't just ignore them!
But I don't have time to rescue everyone!
What do I do?!
The station... and Gojo-sensei...
are just up ahead, too!
Roe!
That vocabulary!
Inumaki-senpai!
Salmon!
Please help!
Salmon, salmon.
Episode 37
Red Scale
Don't move!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
22:10    Shibuya Station, Interior
It Is Dangerous
Tickets
Automatic
Yuji Itadori!
My brothers' killer!
Convergence!
Convergence
Blood Manipulation: "Convergence"
is a skill that involves applying pressure
to blood in order to compress it to its limit.
The blood compressed with Convergence
is then released through a single point.
The initial speed of this blood
enhanced with cursed energy
well exceeds the speed
of sound when released.
This secret art of Blood
Manipulation is called...
Piercing Blood
Piercing Blood.
A double impact?
What an odd technique.
There's something
I have to ask you.
Did my little brothers leave
behind any last words?
Brothers?
Tsk.
I'm talking about the ones you two killed.
No, not really.
But...
They were crying.
Eso!
Kechizu!
Watch over me...
This is your older brother!
Shit...
He got distance on me again.
That beam of blood is too fast.
I have a 50/50 chance to dodge.
If my intuition is off and it hits my head...
I'm dead.
Then I should at least...
determine when he fires it myself.
He's luring me out.
Fine, then.
I knew it!
That attack is only fast when first fired.
Once I avoid it, I can lay on the pressure!
Supernova.
Supernova
Tsk.
I got hasty.
It wasn't compressed enough.
Shit! This bastard...
is strong!
Hey!
Hey! What's the situation?
Mechamaru! What have you been—
Conserving energy.
There's still a lot I need to do.
Choso! Blood Manipulation, huh?
You know about it?
He's using the same
cursed technique as Kamo.
That thin-eyed third year, huh?
Which means...
I don't know its weakness.
Geh!
Blood Manipulation is treasured as one of
the Kamo clan's hereditary techniques.
The reason for that is "Convergence,"
which compresses blood with high pressure,
plus "Piercing Blood" and "Blood Blade,"
which are derived from that,
giving it a well-balanced response
in close, mid, and long range.
Since Choso won't bleed out,
he has no openings.
Thanks for the critical infor—
I don't know its weakness,
but I do have an idea.
What is it?
First, flee into the restroom.
The restroom?! Why?!
I'll explain later.
There's maybe a 10% chance this works.
Sorry, but if this fails,
brace yourself for death.
That's cruel.
At this rate, you'll just get worn
down until you're killed anyway.
Idiot.
That only leads to the
restrooms and the elevator.
No matter which you run to,
you're trapped like a rat.
What's that sound?
This guy has beaten my brothers before.
Those two wouldn't lose to some idiot.
There's also that second voice
that suddenly appeared.
It would be right to assume
he's planning something.
Don't let your guard down.
What's wrong?
Not coming?
You're a coward, huh?
Just like your brothers.
I'll kill you!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
You really are just like them.
All three of you care
so much for each other.
It makes you easy to manipulate.
It's all gone well so far.
Now it's up to chance,
Yuji Itadori!
Too bad.
That was your last chance.
You're the one with nowhere to run now!
Convergence dissolved?!
In order to enhance the effects of
the Blood Manipulation Technique,
users constantly have the coagulation
properties of their blood turned off.
As a result, Choso's blood dissolves in
water more easily than that of others.
On top of that, once exposed to water,
the osmotic pressure causes the red blood
cells to expand and rupture their cell walls.
This left him unable to control the blood
cells that comprise 45% of his blood,
breaking his Convergence.
Mechamaru's aim was on the mark.
In that situation,
it was impossible for Choso to use
Blood Manipulation outside his own body.
Flowing Red Scale - Stack.
Choso lacked combat experience,
so he couldn't comprehend
what was happening to him.
He just coldly accepted the new reality
and conducted his blood
manipulation within his body.
I don't understand the reasoning.
There wasn't any opportunity for me to ask.
But I do know one thing.
I've dragged him into my turf!
I can win!
Choso had been keeping a clot of blood from being exposed and dissolving
in the water as he strengthened
said clot with cursed energy
and compressed the
coagulated lump to its limit,
so the moment Yuji Itadori
was convinced of victory,
it pierced his liver.
Blood Manipulation: Blood Meteorite.
I screwed up! I assumed he couldn't
use any more projectiles!
What now? Where was I hit?
This isn't the same as when
I had a hole in my stomach!
It destroyed something
that shouldn't be broken!
I'm going to lose...
and die!
I understand what my role is.
Fushiguro, Kugisaki,
the other upperclassmen, all of them
will pass through here on
their way to Gojo-sensei.
So even if I die, I'm taking this guy out.
I don't have to be the one
to rescue Gojo-sensei.
Three hits.
A mere three hits,
not counting the ones I guarded against.
Those blows I took from Itadori
dealt this much damage to me...
Blood Meteorite's only
strength is its hardness.
It doesn't have the speed
or impact of Piercing Blood.
If I hadn't caught him by surprise,
it wouldn't have been able to pierce him.
Normally, Blood Manipulation sorcerers
never coagulate blood like
he did for Blood Meteorite.
Even Blood Blade only
solidifies the outline and
circulates blood at high speeds
to heighten its lethality.
Even those sorcerers with
Blood Manipulation can't
extend their concentration
to every blood vessel at once.
So when they strongly coagulate their blood,
it always poses the risk of
causing spontaneous thrombosis.
Bring it.
However, Choso decided the risk
posed by Yuji Itadori was far greater.
He's strong!
A tooth?!
It was a feint?!
Not yet!
I haven't used my left fist since the start.
He probably believes I can't use it anymore.
So this attack using my
right fist as a distraction
will land!
What was that response I felt?
Too bad.
He's still breathing.
Apologize...
to my brothers in the afterlife!
How worthless.
Losing to such riffraff.
What?
In that moment,
memories flooded Choso's mind.
Memories that didn't exist.
Hey!
You, too, Brother!
What's happening? You're...
There he is.
He's alive, right?
Yeah.
Let's get this started, then.
Moan-day?
Monday.
Tuesday!
Mhmm!
Weh-do-ness-day?
Wednesday.
Screw this!
Next time, "Fluctuations."
Next Episode
Fluctuations
Who the hell came up with these readings?!
Someone smarter than you, dummy.